http://www.bettyrides.com/policies/privacy-policy

Privacy policy
BETTY RIDES INC, www.bettyrides.com (the Site). The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for the Site and forms part of our Terms of Use. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you choose not to consent to this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected on the Site. It does not apply to information which we may collect by means other than on the Site.
1. Information We Collect and How It Is Used. AGGREGATE INFORMATION. From time to time, we may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific web page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, and which hyperlinks, if any, they click on. We collect this information through the use of technologies such as cookies and server logs, which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to determine which areas of the Site are most popular and to enhance the Site. We may also group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties, or in response to a government request. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Site. SERVER LOGS. Our servers record your computer's IP address in server logs when you use the Site. We use these logs for statistical tracking and to administer the Site. Your IP address is also used to gather aggregate information about the use of the Site that does not specifically identify you. COOKIES. We use cookies on certain pages of the Site. Cookies are small text files stored on your hard drive, not on the Site. A cookie is not a program, and does not itself have the ability to automatically collect personal information about you. A cookie can store certain information that identifies your browser to our servers in order to make the Site operate more smoothly. For example, when using cookies, you don't have to re-enter your password as frequently when you use the Site. We never save credit card information in cookies. Many cookies we use are session cookies, which means that they are automatically deleted at the end of each session. We also use persistent cookies to keep track of each user's shopping cart information and items to be purchased. You always have the option of disabling cookies using your browser preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. PERSONAL INFORMATION. Voluntary Contact. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, if you send us personal information voluntarily, such as through personal correspondence or emails, we may collect such information. We may use such information to respond to your questions or comments. We may also use such information, and other information that we obtain from your use of the Site, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms of Use agreement. ACCOUNT REGISTRATION/PURCHASES. You are not required to provide any personal information in order to obtain general access to the Site. However, in order to access certain information, services or features contained on the Site, we may require you to provide certain personal information and may give you the option to provide other additional information. For example, if you would like to sign up for our mailing list, make purchases or participate in certain contests, if offered, you may be asked to create an account on the Site and to provide information such as your name, e-mail address, shipping address, and telephone number. As part of the account registration process we may also provide the opportunity for you to share additional personal information such as your gender, date of birth and telephone number. If you choose to make purchases through the Site, you will be asked to provide certain additional information such as your credit card number and its expiration date. Personally identifying information is used to contact you when necessary, to deliver goods purchased through the Site and to process and fulfill any other transactions or services that you request. Financial information that is collected is used only in connection with your purchases and transactions. In addition to using your information as described above, we also may occasionally send you email announcing special promotions, changes in our services, and other information we believe will be of interest to you. You may opt-out of receiving these mailings, or any other e-mails we send to our mailing list, by using the unsubscribe feature in any email you receive from us. If you provide us with the e-mail address of a friend for e-cards provided by the Site (and not through a third party), we will retain your friend's e-mail address only to prevent spamming of that e-mail address and will not use it for any other purpose.
2. Disclosure of Personal Information. We may sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us, such as processing orders and delivering merchandise, sending postal mail and providing marketing assistance and data analysis. We may provide personal information to those businesses when that information is necessary for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform their duties. We may also sometimes form relationships with others, such as promotional partners or sponsors, in order to enhance the information and services on the Site and/or to help promote the Site or for other purposes. From time to time, we may share your e-mail address and other personal information with those parties, and you may receive periodic offers or other communications from them. However, if you have unsubscribed from our e-mail list, or if you indicate on the Site that you do not want us to share your personal information with those parties, then we will not share your personal information with them unless you subsequently opt in to such sharing. In addition, if you have created an account on the Site and if we share your personal information with third parties in accordance with this Privacy Policy, you may subsequently opt out of future information sharing with such parties at any time by logging into your account and updating your profile as further described below. However, please note that opting out of future information sharing with third parties will not affect their use of any information that we might have shared with them before you opted out of such sharing. Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your personal information with any third parties without your prior consent. We cannot, however, ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances without your consent, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications. We can (and you authorize us to) disclose any information about you to law enforcement or other government officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal, may expose us to legal liability, damages, or may harm the Site or any of our visitors. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS. If you are a California resident, California law allows you to request information regarding certain categories of personally identifiable information (for example, but not limited to, you name, postal address and e-mail address) that we may have disclosed to other businesses in the prior calendar year for the other businesses' own direct marketing purposes. You may make a request for this information once each calendar year. To make such a request, please e-mail us at contact@madeindetroit.com with Request for California Privacy Information in the subject line and body of the message. You must provide us with enough information so that we can locate your information in our records. We will send the information covered by the California law to you at the e-mail address from which the request was made.
3. Linked Web Sites. For your convenience, the Site may contain links to other web sites or services. Any information you provide when using such third party web sites or services is collected by them and not by us, and is subject to their privacy practices and not this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other web sites or services, which may differ significantly from our own. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave the Site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. In the event we obtain any information from these outside web sites, our online use of this information will comply with the terms of this Privacy Policy.
4. Security. The Site has physical, procedural and electronic security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. If you create an account on the Site, your account information is protected by a password chosen by you. Access to your online account requires your password. We recommend that you do not disclose your password to any other person. In addition, when you make a purchase using a credit card, we encrypt your credit card number and store it in a secure database protected by a firewall. The transmission of this information is also secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Notwithstanding these efforts, we caution you that "perfect security" does not exist on the Internet.
5. Options / Corrections / Updates. The Site gives you the following options for reviewing, updating or deleting your information from our database: 1. You can review and edit your orders and preferences by logging in at http://www.madeindetroit.com 2. You can opt-in to receive communications from us simply by registering with our site. 3. You can opt-out of receiving promotional email from us by using the unsubscribe feature in any email you receive from us.
6. Children's Privacy Policies (Users Under Age 13). We do not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from children under the age of 13 on the Site, except for the limited circumstances described below. In the event a child under the age of 13 submits a question to us on the Site and identifies his or her age, we may use the child's e-mail address for the sole purpose of responding to the child's question on a one-time-only basis. However, we will not use the child's e-mail address to contact the child and we will delete it from our records once we have responded.
7. Changes To These Terms. The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time without prior notice to you, so please check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
8. Contacting Us. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, your dealings with the Site, or any questions you may contact us at:
BETTY RIDES INC.1834 SE 58th AVEPORTLAND, OR 97215 info@bettyrides.com
Choosing a selection results in a full page refresh.
Press the space key then arrow keys to make a selection.
Use left/right arrows to navigate the slideshow or swipe left/right if using a mobile device
